Jedidia Bagunu

bagunujedidia@gmail.com

09395978033

linkedin.com/in/jedidia-bagunu-2647ba250

https://jedbagunu.github.io/web-portfolio/

Summary

I previously worked at Accenture in the Philippines as Platform Experience Associate for more than 2 years then took certification of intensive training in Web Development at Zuitt Bootcamp to career shift. I am now a certified Fullstack Web Developer and currently looking for a job to nurture my foundation in website development.

Experience

Zuit - Coding Bootcamp Philippines

Zuitt - Coding Bootcamp

Sep 2022 - Oct 2022 (2 months)

Portfolio

- Created Responsive Website showcasing our Portfolio
- Used HTML, CSS and Bootstrap to build the website

API

- Created an e-commerce API
- -Used JSON, Postman API, MongoDB, Node.js, Express.js, Minimum Viable Product(MVP), JWT E-commerce Website
- Fully functioning e-commerce website
- -Used MERN stack

Platform Experience Associate

Accenture in the Philippines

Nov 2019 - Jun 2022 (2 years 8 months)

Evaluate reported content that is flagged for actions with speed, quality and accuracy

Education

Zuitt - Coding Bootcamp

Postgraduate/ Certification, Web Development

Sep 2022 - Oct 2022

Isabela State University

Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering, Computer Software Engineering Jun 2017 - Apr 2019

Skills

Document Object Model (DOM) • NoSQL • Back-End Web Development • JSON • JavaScript • MERN Stack • Front-End Development